Thank you for watching!
Bo N picked
first choice banana
I'm desarrolling now.........
shoes
Yay!
happy bread day!
Happy Bread Day!
Today's project, please!
Here we go!
Thoughtful thoughts to you, big brother gift teacher!
Happy Bread Day!
I'm in trouble. I'm turning 50.
Fifty?
Yes, Himura-san is 53.
I'm 51.
You can't lie so subtly.
If you're going to say it, hold the top one.
Bananaman celebrated birthdays in April and May
For either of those two
The members bought gifts on their own with a budget of 5,000 yen as a guideline.
Then, Bananaman looked at the gifts given out and
Bananaman looked at the gifts and guessed which one was the gift for which person.
If he guesses wrong, Bananaman buys the gift with his own money
And he will be paid for it.
I don't like the idea of buying something for someone else.
Okay, okay.
Then what member wants me to get it wrong?
Oh, no!
Oh, Mr. Kimura's gone.
Hello, Mr. Kimura.
Mr. Kimura.
Hello.
So cute!
What's this? It's the middle of the moon.
Yes, it's like that, isn't it?
If you've gone as far as you can go... you can have something like this... as a memory.
As a memory.
I thought it would be nice if you could keep it in a corner of your mind as a memory.
You can buy this for 5,000 yen.
I've got it.
What?
I got a moon certificate once.
At first I thought you didn't look like me.
I wonder if I'm easy to give the moon to.
I see.
If that's the case... well... that's what I was thinking.
You're like the moon.
I wonder which one it is.
I've received one before.
If you've received one, then maybe you have an idea to give it to someone.
This is so hard.
This is very difficult.
That's the point.
It sounds like you've already gone too far.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean, compared to me.
What do you mean?
The one who's already gone.
I don't have any more stuff.
You're on the verge of death.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I thought it was kind of on point.
But it's not stylish.
It is.
It's fashionable.
That's why I don't think it's coming to me.
It's stylish.
I don't know why I'm getting this.
It's a blur.
I get the idea that this precedent will make it easier to give Hime-san and the moon.
This is so hard!
I don't want to miss the first one.
Please guess for sure!
I'm sure you'll guess it.
Surprisingly, Hime-san seems more pleased with this kind of thing.
You're right.
No, no, no, it's me.
I thought you'd be happy with this.
I don't think I'd enjoy it.
I see.
Whose?
He's probably saying, "You're not really going to get it, are you?
He's saying that.
But you'd be surprised, I'm a romantic.
Every time I look up, I see my land.
Do you know anything about the universe?
Space.
I love space.
I love space.You know I love space, right?
You have a lot of space talk.
I don't have a lot of space talk.
So, wow, I don't know, seriously.
No, I want to guess.
I can't tell you who it is either.
I think I might know who she is if I ask her.
Yeah, I think she's a little older than you.
Me, too.
It's not a litter.
Sorry about the litter.
I don't think they're gonna reach that.
They're not kids yet.
You're still a kid.
I think she's a little older now.
You're used to getting presents like this.
This is so much fun.
We're the only ones having this much fun.
I'm so glad you guys are having such a good time.
Is it me?
That's what I thought.
I thought if it was a jigsaw puzzle, it would be me.
I like jigsaw puzzles.
If it was me, it would be me.
Me.
Okay.
This is Land of the Moon.
I believe this gift is for me, Sitara.
First of all, I'd like to announce the giver of this gift.
Who bought it?
Who?
Yes, I did.
You got this.
Ume.
I thought this was really plum.
Stylish... land of the moon.
What a nice present!
Yes, sir.
So romantic!
A romantic gift from Umezawa.
Is this for Sitara?
I wanted to give her a present.
It's for Sitara's big brother
Yay!
I knew it! How was it?
Oh, yeah.
Why did you get me this one?
Is that it?
You were thinking of buying me a present.
You already started looking?
Yes, I thought it would be for you.
He's a romantic.
You know me.
Of course.
She even confessed that her love for you is beautiful.
It's a little romantic.
There's nothing in the world I can buy anymore.
Maybe I can.
I knew I was right.
But there are so many opportunities to look up at the moon.
On the way home...
When I'm sentimental, I look up at the moon.
It's like, "There's my land.
When you look up at the moon from now on...
I'm sure you'll think of me, too.
I'm confessing to you.
I love you.
I have land on the moon, and so does Mr. Himura.
That's right.
Just the two of us.
I'm glad it was 1-0.
It could have been 2-0.
I have one.
I would've had one.
You've got two.
Right this way. Ta-da!
Wow.
This is tough.
I thought it was Mr. Himura the moment I opened it.
But now that I have this...
It's decided.
It's not me. It's not me. It's not me.
It's not me.
No, this is completely...
I thought this was completely set for Mr. Nimura.
Marumiya's sukiyaki.
I love their sukiyaki sprinkles.
Hee...Heh.
Do you have this?
I used to wear this when I was really little.
My brother would say.
My brother would say, "You put too much on it.
As an adult, I still put a little bit on it.
I still want to eat it.
I still want to eat it so bad I want you to put on rice.
I'm sure of it.
Have you ever had this?
Marumiya is famous for noritama.
But their sukiyaki is better.
You should try it.
And I'm sure you'll love it.
Date Masamune is Miyagi's rice.
Date Masamune is on the radio.
Date Masamune.
That's right.
Sendai's Raiyu.
This one too.
110% Hikaru-san!
Rice Accompaniment Set
I've recently become addicted to the rice accompaniment set.
I chose a 5,000 yen set of rice to go with the rice.
I'm sure you'll love it because it's so delicious!
I'm not even confused about this!
But...
If I had to put it simply, I'd say Mr. Himura.
Rice and rice accompaniments are
That's why this is all I have!
I've got it all here in Sendai.
But this is all here.
I'm Noritama!
I'm not lost.
No, it's me.
The fact that I have this...
It's the biggest thing.
Laughs.
I think so, too.
If we're not talking about it here, I think we're talking about it on the radio.
He's talking.
So if you're Kubo, listen to the radio.
I heard that you like this one, so I put it in.
I can see that.
But...
I wonder if she'll put two in a row.
Wait a minute... maybe he only has mine.
No, I think they might be trying to pull something like that on us.
I don't think you should think of it that way.
I've been talking about it for a while now.
LOL.
If you think "Han-han" means me 5 out of 10 times.
I could be wrong.
That's hard.
But it's me.
I think the clue is in the "openings".
It's an easy problem.
This is the reason why this set of rice accompaniments
I think it's Kubo's present to me.
I think it's Kubo's present!
And I already guessed...
Kubo!
100% Kubo!
I've heard why on the radio.
I could read that much.
Who got it right?
Me.
I'm totally fine now
I won so far.
A set of rice with tsukiaki furikake
Is this a present for Shirara?
I wanted to give her a present for
Brother Himura.
That's a lie.
Why? Why?
It's sad.
I knew it.
I'll do it.
You're lying.
I'll do it!
I thought it was Mr. Himura the moment I opened it, but here it is.
Then why did you put this in?
What's this?
I wanted to give Mr. Himura a set of rice bowls as a gift.I first wanted to give Mr. Himura a set of rice bowls as a gift.
That's exactly what I was thinking at the time.
I heard on the radio that
I knew that Shara-san liked Marumiya's Tsukiaki.
I knew he liked it.
I wondered if you liked it too.
I told you, right?
I'm Noritama.
I like this too.
I haven't heard that from many other people.
I like this more than anyone else in show business.
I grew up with it.
Really?
I've been thinking about that possibility.
I grew up on these too.
I definitely grew up on this Marumiya Tsukiaki for breakfast.
That's part of the reason.
I'm sure it was the same for you.
I should've thought of a pattern.
I don't know about that.
Tsuki-aki, that's me.
That's Noritama!
Remember...
Noritama!
Remember me!
But I was so sad.
If it had been me all along, I wouldn't have known what it meant.
I love you so much.
I worked so hard to choose you.
It wasn't me.
Fate is a bitch.
I thought I was at my limit.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What the hell?
That project, Mr. Himura?
Surprisingly, it's not just fun.
I'm sorry.
It was hard work.
I'm at my wits' end.
I'm getting there. I'm getting pretty close.
I'll have to do it again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just remember...
Glueballs.
Here we go!
Ready?
Don!
Oh, clothes!
I don't know about clothes...
Oh, you don't mean clothes?
No, no, no. Clothes.
Lounging clothes.
This is definitely something like that.
Cute.
Which one is it?
Maybe the size will tell us.
Oh, a belly band.
It's not thin?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But it's Mr. Himura.
He's wearing pajamas and a belly band, so he's using it as loungewear.
I really got the image of you wearing pajamas.
I want you to wear comfortable pajamas.
This is surely amazing?
I want you to protect your belly with a belly wrap
I chose a design that suits you.
It's a belly wrap!
A belly wrap makes me feel like me.
You said "belly wrap".
No, I didn't.
I have a few of those... three of them.
He sleeps with it wrapped around his stomach.
Yeah, yeah, I wear a belly wrap.
That's a big one.
No, that's me.
XL, so you're Mr. Himura.
Isn't this still too small?
But a belly band fits tight.
It's more like a belly band.
That's right.
When you're sleeping.
That's why.
The image of sleeping...
Mr. Himura, in padaka.
Sleeping on soaked concrete.
That's a hippopotamus.
You have to hose him down.
That's the image of a hippo.
That's me.This is me.
Me, me, me.
I'm pretty sure that's me.
This is me with a belly band.
I think the design looks like Mr. Himura.
His nose is kind of popped open.
It's bright.
It's a belly band.
It's all about who has the bigger belly.
Who has the bigger belly?
Me.
The big brother who gets this present is...
I'm Himura.
So...
Who bought this present for me?
Yes, sir.
Ah! Endo.
Thank you, Endo!
I'm so happy.
Endo's choice loungewear and stomach wrap set!
Is it a present for Himura as per the size?
I wanted to give him a gift.
It's Himura's big brother
Yay!
Yay Tememu!
That was close!
Thank goodness it was close!
Why did I choose this one?
I thought of Himura-san relaxing at home
I thought she would be wearing pajamas.
Also, the design is very Himura-esque.
I'm glad I'm like that.
It's kind of bright, isn't it?
It's like an open nose, right?
What's the point of the belly band?
I like Himura-san's belly.
I wonder if this will work.
I don't know.
It's stretchy.
I wanted it to keep you warm and protect you.
It stretches.
It's cute.
Plenty of room.
It's so good.
It's amazing.
It warms me up so much!
I love it.
I didn't know this existed.
It's so good!
I didn't know they did this.
I imagined it would be like this.
Come here, come here.
It's great.
It's great, but...
You're gonna touch it?
No, it's fine.
Touch it.
I don't understand.
I don't get it.
It's like glam rock.
It's funny.
When people aren't listening at all.
It's like flower rock.
I touched it.
Not great.
I like it.
What an exchange!
A crazy gift from an unexpected angle.
The giver of the gift...
Next Episode
Ready, set, go!
What?
T-shirt?
It's me.
It's cute.
Yes, it is.
You're Mr. Himura, right?
I'm me, right?
I mean handmade T-shirts.
I'm sure you have everything you need.
I thought it was important to be unexpected
I decided to make one with an original design
I hope you'll wear it as everyday wear, not loungewear
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's for everyday wear.
This one's an XL, too.
I'm Mr. Himura, after all.I don't care what you think, it's Mr. Himura.
Even this one has what looks like a mole.
It's his hair, right?
But he's got this weird idea about Mr. Himura.
They're going that way.
Have we seen this touch before?
Yoda?
Yoda's gonna do it.
Whoever came up with this idea...
This is so Yoda.
No one like Kaki or Inoue would draw this.
On purpose?
It's not half-baked or deliberate.
It's terrible.
It's definitely Mr. Himura.
If it were me, I'd be really crazy.
But he'd probably say something like, "Keep Himura on your chest.
Then you won't win anymore.
You said "outside clothes.
He said, "Please put this on outside.
I can't even wear it inside.
What will my family say?
Look, Mr. Himura, this is Mr. Himura.
Here's a T-shirt for you, and I'm Himura.
Raise your hand who'll get this?
Raise your hand.
Ohhh...
Wait a minute.
I didn't expect this.
It's like this?
Well, my touch hasn't changed since elementary school.
I bet your touch hasn't changed.
This is definitely not good.
I don't know what kind of a thing this is.
Original T-shirt designed by Kawasaki
Is it Himura who wants you to wear it in style?
I wanted to give him a gift.
Shimoda's brother.
Wow!
Here it is.
I can't guess.
Why is this Mr. Himura's?
What's this?
I knew it... Shimoda-san...
That charming image...
I thought it was necessary.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
What do you mean?
What do you mean, the charming part is missing?
If you take a look at the picture of the two of them...
Which do you want them to go?
Mr. Shimoda, who would never wear it.
Ms. Shimoda would never wear something like this.
If she wears this, she'll be charming.
There won't be any works by the two of them.
So it's not charming now.
Now this...
I've put a little bit of charm into it.
But it's still not charming.
But...
When I put this on...
Well...
Charming.
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
It's an accent.
Charming.
We'll go around back like this.
There it is.
Well, well, well.
He's saying his name.
I'm so happy for you, but you're not going to win this.
You know, I think we all know who this guy is.
Who are you? - I know who you are.
I get it.
Some of you didn't.
I thought it was all your drawings.
I didn't know your drawings were like this.
But among the Gosei students, this touch is already called "Kawasaki Sakura".
I'm sure she'll be very active if there is a drawing project in the future.
If you couldn't win a present for yourself
I'll buy it with my own money.
Here is the next present!
Here we go!
What?
Huh?
Oh!
Oh, that banana art, it's so cute.Ohhhh, that banana art... so cute.
Goo. No, no, no, no, no.
No, but... on a plain one, it's not just the banana that stands out, it's the brown one.
It took me so long to do it.
No, it's not there. It's in there.
That's why you went there so long ago... and this place is already number 9.
I'm sure money can buy anything, so I bought some bananas for a laugh and a banner art to express my feelings for Ohara Mita City.
It was a luxury banana!
I'm sure this is the one... well, I'm sure it's the one... if it was Mr. Himura, I don't know what it means.
I'm sure it's me... and I'm sure it's great.
I'm sure you'll be able to find the right one for you.
I'm sure I'll get a present from you.
I'm sure I'll get a present.
Who's it going to be?
It's the other way around...
Is that the opposite of what you just said?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Is it the other way around?
Is Iyoki's masterpiece banana art a present for Shirara?
Is this the gift you got for her?
I wanted to give her a present.
It was Stara's brother.
I won!
Thank you very much!
I'm glad it was straight.
I bought myself a banana for practice.
Seriously?
You did a lot.
There are so many!
There's even one that's full of bananas!
That's amazing!
I thought we had a happy birthday.
That's great!
It's behind Mr. Chitara's.
It's in the back.
A thumbnail.
It says "Chitara" on the back.
"Chitara" is a rare name, isn't it?
It's not nice to meet you.
But... it's great... but why and when?
When did you get this?
The pot was harvested yesterday.
Yesterday.
Yesterday... but the sugar content is really high.
There's so much sugar in the chugger spot.
I woke up this morning and it's not good.
They're 600 yen a bottle.
Here...
this one
That's why I buy them. They're high in sugar.
So how long does it take?
Oh, about three hours yesterday.
Three hours for this.
That's great.
I'll take it.
Oh, look at that.
Just right.
I'm okay with this, right?
For a second there, it was the other way around.
The T-shirt and the T-shirt.
I have a T-shirt.
And a T-shirt.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Sweet.
This one's electronic.
Yes, it is.
It's some kind of regular supermarket.
These aren't that expensive.
Like 50 yen a bottle.
And they're not that good.
It's really good!
I'm starting to feel like Hideo Noguchi!
Sight Asuka's graduation concert was held at the Tokyo Dome!
Thank you very much for your support!
SightAska's photo book will be released on May 23rd!
Next time, presents full of love will appear one after another!
What will win the heart of a banana?
Please subscribe to our channel and
Good Button!
See you soon!
See you later.
See you again.
And again.
and again
and againagain (and again)
again (and again)
and also
First Venue
First venue